<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>fabisblog</title>
    <description>A minimal hugo theme focus on content</description>
    <link>https://fabisblog.com</link>
    
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 121212, Calvin Tran</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:03:17 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Hugo - gohugo.io</generator>
    <docs>http://cyber.harvard.edu/rss/rss.html</docs>
    <atom:link href="https://fabisblog.com/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>In Awe Of Life</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/in_awe_of_life/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Awe Of Life&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How can it be so beautiful, day after day… all this is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spending time with friends. Seeing the flower grow out of those tiny little cracks in the concrete. Hearing people laugh. Seeing the sun rise up. Preparing the nutritious meal for after the workout. Laying in bed to fall asleep. Rising out of bed in the morning, really grumpy and not wanting to go. Is it not this beautiful game called life?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reverence, gratitude and awe for life. For everything that happens. Thats what I want to be known for. For embracing it all, never backing up, never shying away from the challenges being presented to me. I go through this earth school in love, courage and faith.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What are my footprints that I am leaving behind? I hope they are good. I try to make sure that they are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lately, these past couple of days I am thinking about realizing our full potential. I think there is sooo much in every single one of us. So much love, courage, confidence, self esteem we can tap into. So much of it we can use to create and shape our life the way we desire it to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the best thing is&amp;hellip; that I already see the poeple close to me doing it. They really shine. Incredibly proud of you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lets go out, and make things happen. Every one of us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/in_awe_of_life/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:03:17 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Day, Another Blessing</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/another_dayanother_blessing/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What a day! Even though I went to work, all was normal… but, you know, the energy was just right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My day started off kind of really mad. Things did not seem to go my way, for like an hour, maybe two. In those moments, I really like being just mad and letting it off. Not off onto others of course, but venting and being real is very important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later on, the energy started flowing. I had great conversations all day long, so much laughter, fun, compassion, things were just going my way… I made them go my way. All was good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After work, I eat right, to fuel me well. I laid down and took a short nap. After that, I went full on focus to do my things. You know, writing, chess, workouts, ice bathing, and so an. I go where the energy flows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, ice baths. I take them regularly. Very often. Almost every day, I just hop in my tub full of water, staying outside in the winter. Man, is it a blessing to experience things like that. The power is real. I am gonna elaborate on ice bathing and its benefits on the mind and body in another text, I am sure of that. It’s gotta be said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, just a normal day. What a blessing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wishing you love, power, excitement. And a good night sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/another_dayanother_blessing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 22:07:02 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Focus And Attention</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/focus_and_attention/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I love to exercise my focus, concentration and attention span. To sit and focus on something for more like 15 minutes is something not so common anymore in our society.
 You see it in high performing people. But not really in the regular one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love to give my best. I love a laser clear focus. When my brain is ON.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have just completed my first online chess tournament. It lasted for 3.5 hours. After 3 hours, my brain was jelly. To hold up that kind of concentration for a prolonged period of time is something I admire, and it is not too easy to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I find that we can exercise our concentration and attention span. That is why I play chess, read books, listen to podcasts, write, and so on. Most of the day, my brain is on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It gives me this good feeling of purpose and improvement in every single day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am gonna continue to give my best. To be the most knowledgeable person I can be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is good for me and my self esteem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS: Good sleep and good nutrition really helps us to focus and perform at our best, both physically and mentally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/focus_and_attention/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 21:46:07 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Can I Give?</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/what_can_i_give/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Asking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What can I give?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What can I do more of?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What can I do for you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To give, it is my only purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No answer today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/what_can_i_give/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 21:48:43 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Me</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/emotional_me/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I don’t know if Christmas did this to me, but somehow I am super emotional about my family and friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have spend a good evening with three of my closest friends in the living room. Fire was burning slow in the chimney. No music was on. Just we. The three of us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I consider this a pure blessing in life. I thank you, my friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So emotional. What good can I do for you? Is it enough?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are deserving of the world and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sitting upstairs in my room. Hearing the laughter from down there. The laughter of you, soothing my soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/emotional_me/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 21:07:59 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just An Update</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/just_an_update/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a little update. I can already feel that it has been a couple of days with no entry on my page. It feels like a long time, so my wish to write and give and update on here is gonna be fulfilled right away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Making wishes come true and fact in the world, non stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feels so wonderful to have a space just to write and let out. This is my space to do that. What a great and pacifying feeling that it gives me. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, Christmas Days were lovely. I mean… so much that these days have meant to me. So much. I love my family beyond. I thank you, from the bottom of me heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The days are going pretty well for me. I am on track. It’s like I feel so full… Everything makes sense. I feel as if I am the richest man on earth. Again, I give thanks for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Man, too much on my heart. Just sitting here in peace. Enjoying the moment. Feeling stronger than I have ever before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am gonna pick up the thousand page book laying to my side and read it until I fall asleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wish you a good night, a good day, and a good life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/just_an_update/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 21:54:13 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friends With The Struggle</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/friends_with_the_struggle/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I really, really am friends with the struggle. Good with the darkness. With the bad times. I know them very well. Of course I don’t like it. Of course. BUT - full acceptance is somehow making it easier. Way less overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One kind of the weakest people around here are the ones only running around from one pleasure to another- you can smell the fear already. But they keep on running, running and looking for the things bringing pleasure, dopamine, fun. May it be partying, drugs, food, television, sex, social media, over exercising, workaholism, you name it…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They cannot bear a second of silence. It is terrifying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the crash is always coming. And then the spiral begins anew.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My life goes the best just being up to date. Up to the moment. No shit in denial. No fears lingering around. When it comes - it comes. Then its time to face it and be am man. Going thru it. Making the best out of it. Learning. Pondering. Keeping on going. Getting things right again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But running away… always ends in disaster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be brave. Look. Go through it. Whatever it takes. Commit. Make your life great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again… I believe so much in us. I believe in the love and power of every single one of us. I wanna see us strong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/friends_with_the_struggle/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 21:27:36 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poor Choices</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/poor_choices/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the past few days I made some bad choices a couple of times. Why do I keep doing that shit I am asking myself? Come on, really time to step up my game. Thats not me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very mad at myself. Time to get outta here, quick. I know I can do it. I have proven great things to myself already. And I am gonna keep on forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/poor_choices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 17:31:17 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mind Is Clear</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/the_mind_is_clear/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nah, today was pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At a point I just sat there for like 30 minutes, breathing deep, feeling, and considering. Just being. Letting it flow. Was really beautiful. Bits of pain here and there, but it’s needed, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being close to going to sleep now I look back at these hours. I even got a whole lotta shit done! A lot. Working towards these goals, so so so much. Everyday, putting in the work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mind is clear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/the_mind_is_clear/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 21:49:13 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laying Low, pt.2</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/laying_low_pt.2/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today some things came up again. I was sitting in grief, reflecting. Looking at chances I could have taken. Well, kind of laying low again today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I find interesting is that grief and laying low does not chance the fact of a good day. I sit here in gratitude and presence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The worst is to be split. To put on a smile while wanting to cry. That is really really bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But being present? Acknowledging the fears? That full on ok for me. I can handle myself pretty well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I went to my favorite market, buying the best produce (veggies, fruit, some meat) I can possibly find. The best around here. I don’t care the price. I am worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I heat up my room. I check all the stuff on my to do list. Slowly I get it done. All in peace. So my mind is clear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peace of mind. The highest human good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/laying_low_pt.2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 15:51:27 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Feel Great (thought)</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/i_feel_great/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Of course I am very good in life. I feel fantastic. It only makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my highest values is hard work. I don&amp;rsquo;t take anything for granted, If I want something, I go and get it. I deserve it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am taking care very well of me. I work out at least 3 times a week, to look good, be strong, and keep my masculine hormones all intact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I eat well. Almost no junkfood. I avoid sugar, and to a great deal I only eat natural foods, which did not went through a factory. I avoid chemicals at all costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I take care of my mind. I read books. I listen to podcasts. Everyday, my mind brings up new ideas. I feed my brain very well. Additionally, I am an expert at taking care of my emotional state. If I do not feel well, I instantly take the time to refresh, work on me and put myself in order again. I face my fears on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I face my fears on a daily basis. What’s left to be afraid of? Not much. The past couple of weeks I am enjoying a beautiful state of fearlessness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel very powerful. In the sense that I am in control of my life. I decide what I do, what I say, wether I go left or right. I am in charge and the boss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love the people I am with on a daily basis. Except from work where I cannot always choose, I am surrounded by beautiful beings. My friends, my family, it is just perfect. I feel right in place and I love them so much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyday, I can honestly say that I give my best. Of course there are bad days. Of course. But I am not afraid. Thats ok. I take my time. I rest. I recover. Until life gives me so much energy again. It never seems to end. Ongoing fountain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can take everything away from me. Sit me naked in the desert. I know, that I am gonna come back and build my life back up again. The riches in my heart can never be taken away from me. I pray. I pray. I thank god. He seemed to put something inside of me. Some kind of light. Some kind of love. Some kind of blessing. And it is my duty not to keep it for my own. It is my duty to share the light everywhere I go. In form of a hug, a smile, a kind word… maybe even a serious one if it helps. I just gotta stay true to who I am. Thats what I have to do in life. Priority number one.
No money, no external validation. Nothing like that. No interest. Just give me my peace of mind. Thats what I am about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe that everybody can just feel great. If we put in the work. It actually takes work. It may be a long way… but it is possible. Step by step. I am on this road for 8 years now. I started thinking when I was 17.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel like I wanna hug the whole world. And release it from all the bullshit. Actually, 98% of the things we do really don’t even matter. Let&amp;rsquo;s focus on the 2% that do. Entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/i_feel_great/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:12:09 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grief, Tears Of Joy</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/grief_tears_of_joy/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How can it be so sweet and bitter at the same time? Sitting here, in grief, with tears of joy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave. I want to stay, the moment never passing. The weekend going on forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, the manifestation of being in the right place, at the right time, with the right people. That feeling of… fullness, and connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I have to go. Waking up early in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/grief_tears_of_joy/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 15:32:05 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Things First</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/first_things_first/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What I have realized is that my mental and emotional state ALWAYS comes first. At any day, point, and situation in life. When I feel like it… I do it. Even when I am at work. Even when something important is happening. For a minute I go outside. I take deep breaths. I feel. I center myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There I go again. Here I am. Fresh. Full of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes something hits us in daily life - and we shake. What was that? We may ask ourselves. Or maybe we know very well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some kind of trigger. Someone laughing in the back. Some thing you see. Something that somehow resonates and triggers YOU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t think that you have to react, or be, this or any other way…  Don’t think that you have to endure the negativity and when its over THEN you will relax and calm down. Do it NOW. And see life unfolding in &lt;em&gt;new ways&lt;/em&gt;. YOUR ways!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we ignore and simply move on - we lose our presence. Our power. Our authenticity. And this comes with a huge price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make the world a product of you, not yourself a product of the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, please please please, put yourself FIRST! YOU ARE WORTH IT. You are doing yourself and everybody around a great honor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I appreciate you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a good day,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/first_things_first/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 20:40:12 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dopamine Kicks Ruin Lives</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/dopamine_kicks_ruin_lives/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My theory is that the more artificial dopamine we consume, produce and exert… the more fucked up and unhappy we get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The more social media scrolling, smoking, drinking, porn, sugar, overeating, youtube videos, Netflix, thousand selfies, and so on, you name it… the more we burn out. The list can go on forever in this modern world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think there is nothing wrong with all these things itself. It is HOW we use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many many people are using all those things to numb themselves. To numb the pain. To get the next dopamine kick. And the next. And the next. Until we crash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I find that NONE of these things listed above REALLY make me happy. Sometimes they are fun. Until it&amp;rsquo;s enough. No more interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I find which REALLY makes me happy is authentic self expression… which comes from within. I mean things like creativity, writing, drawing, connecting and spending time with people, working out, feeling my body, reading, going out into nature, just being…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of that stuff it is for me. Most of the time I am actually doing things that are &lt;em&gt;meaningful&lt;/em&gt; to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To me. Everybody is an individual. And you gotta figure out the stuff that &lt;em&gt;REALLY&lt;/em&gt; makes you happy and &lt;em&gt;fulfilled&lt;/em&gt; in life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watch out for all these tiny little addictive dopamine kicks. They never fill us up. They are endless cravings. They ruin lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/dopamine_kicks_ruin_lives/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 22:02:51 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laying Low</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/laying_low/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;today was a day I was laying very low. After a weekend of traveling, a day has come to just sleep, recover, and catch up at what happened these busy past few days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before going to sleep soon I am reading some beautiful lines here in front of me, which I feel like sharing with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;„Whatsoever a man soweth that shall he also reap.This means that whatever man sends out in the world or deed, will return to him; what he gives, he will receive.
If he gives hate, he will receive hate; if he gives love; he will receive love; if he gives criticism, he will receive criticism; if he lies he will be lied to; if he cheats he will be cheated. We are taught also, that the imaging faculty plays a leading part in the game of life.
Keep thy heart (or imagination) with all diligence, for out of it are the issues of life“&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quoted from „The writings of Florence Scovel Shinn“.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look back at my weekend. The years. My friends, my life. What have I created? What have I received? Most importantly, what did I give?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are unbelievable amounts of gratitude which I can feel. So much joy. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, I feel for the things that I gave which have created pain in the world. I am sorry. I was weak and stupid. I will do anything in my power to get strong and create more of the good. Because thats for what I am here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To take ownership and responsibility for all that happens to me… heaven and hell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To take ownership and responsibility for all that happens to me… I would choose no differently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/laying_low/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 22:02:48 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do As You Please</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/do_as_you_please/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We all know that guy who is always tired. That guy who seems to love to sleep on the table in school. Even though he already had his 11 hours at night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know the cause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we do not create our lives by how we personally feel and think, we experience &lt;em&gt;a loss of energy.&lt;/em&gt;  We are a victim of circumstance. We get tired, bored, or even stressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cure for that is to proactively create the situation to how we desire it to be. With and through presence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Presence is the answer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creating reality requires strength. Independence. Self esteem. Values which I would love to see more of in this modern world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The good news is that we &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; get our strength back, if we have lost it somehow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The answer is to live by our own inspiration (&amp;amp; imagination). And to build up our self esteem again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In all areas of my life (work, relationship, sport, art, etc.), I like to do things just the way I want them to be. I decide. I do as I please. (And that does not necessarily exclude a compromise!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That puts us in a state of energy, presence, fullness, confidence, and fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can hear people scream that we just cannot do as we please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tell you that we can. Otherwise, life is going to be a disaster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the first place, who the fuck tells you what to do? And why do people believe they can’t be doing what they truly desire? The system is coming for you. Watch out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decide that my life is mine. I do as I please. I do what I think is best for me and the world. And I also want to see people strong and inspired building their life the way they wish it to be, day by day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a good one!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/do_as_you_please/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 21:21:21 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overflow</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/overflow/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is a day, I feel like a a fountain spilling over and over with no end in sight. Like an endless machine full of ideas, new thoughts, focus, energy, inspiration, authenticity, courage, and so on…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s day’s like these when I am feeling so full and alive. After unlearning lots and lots of shit that society threw upon me, I peeled many layers of that onion to get to the core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still happening. Still working on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our core is full of love. Inspiration. Imagination. Creativity. And first and foremost, the measure of it all: &lt;em&gt;energy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, children are fascinating to me. Look at them, running around all day long, having ideas with no end… the energy they exert, that pure confidence, presence, and incredibly high self esteem. They come so pure. Natural. It is truly amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is &lt;em&gt;before the system&lt;/em&gt; got a hold of them and swallowed them as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I truly believe that this innate energy that children express so naturally is who we truly are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s get back to the core. To infinite fun, love, confidence, presence, and everything which you truly desire in life!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/overflow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 20:03:51 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reality (Visions)</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/reality_visions/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Reality is so… formable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walking through days seeing infinite possible realities potentially unfolding…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;which one do we choose?&lt;br&gt;
which one do you wish for?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Infinite numbers of ways to act… choosing accordingly to soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right or left? Up or down? Kind or angry? &lt;em&gt;Full or empty&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find those who are yours…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which we &lt;em&gt;choose&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/reality_visions/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 17:55:38 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freshness</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/freshness/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The past couple days I have this feeling of freshness over me…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I see the world with &lt;em&gt;brand&lt;/em&gt; new eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My brand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I see infinite numbers of possible ways for reality to unfold right here and now… and, I got to choose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have never felt it that intense before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am on my way to unlocking imagination on a different kind of level again. Remember the days filled with rainbows? You were very, very young.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It feels like I am getting back there again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These past few days I have been enjoying perfect absence of any kind of fear. I mean it. These days are up there with ones of the best of my life. And nothing spectacular even happened. It is within me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can I create more of that I ask myself?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though my sight is clear… new questions arising on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is it the endless flow of life?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/freshness/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 17:55:05 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing It is</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/writing_it_is/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For such a long time I contain that desire to write. It is living within me. Burning high. I have just read a piece from a year ago expressing that feeling so clearly. It was as if I wrote it just an hour ago. I remember so vividly, going my way through the woods, not far from home. I am coming closer and that feeling for writing is rising up. &amp;ldquo;Hi, here I am again!&amp;rdquo;. What a moment of beauty and presence. What a beautiful moment of indulging in desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I feel at home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/writing_it_is/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 20:58:39 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live And Tell Your Truth</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/live_and_tell_your_truth/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is our duty! To live, speak and tell our truth, which we have found. But this in itself requires us to go through a journey.. a journey of self discovery. A discovery of who we are and what we stand for. A really famous and definitely one of my favorite quotes I have ever heard is „a man who won’t stand for something will fall for anything“. And it&amp;rsquo;s true. Not only for men. It is for everybody. And I really respect people who got that thing, and everyday I make sure that I am one of them as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To stand for something gives you power. It gives you a point in life. It gives you YOUR point and power in life!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am writing FOR people. I am rooting FOR you! For your unique and individual power, strengths, qualities, values, character, and so on… I want to see people strong. Healthy. Free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know the sheer power within every single one of us. Many times, I believe in people even more than they believe in themselves. Because I know where I came from. The mental and physical state I have been in. I know how it feels like to be depressed, weak, unworthy, anxious, lost…
BUT on the other hand, I know even more how it feels to be strong, healthy, fit, confident, free, HAPPY, grateful, powerful… &lt;em&gt;fulfilled&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I kind of know whats possible. I have experienced how far we can climb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe that, at least potentially, every person, YOU, got soooooooo much energy inside. You can move things. You can impact. You can create your life beyond any limit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wish you a wonderful and powerful day, and a good journey in this life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/live_and_tell_your_truth/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 20:19:47 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Another Piece</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/just_another_piece/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;God, I feel like I’ve been doing this forever already. Hah! Just a-nother piece (insert singing voice). I’m tired. Which is good. I had a good day. Fuck, it was great to be honest. I ate well, trained hard, connected with people, learned some new things, did what I am supposed to do. I kind of even „broke a record“. Our trainer told us that in many years only 3 people did a rope swing from one section to another, at a certain distance. I took the challenge and did it as well. I felt like I could go even further. Well, was fun. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the end of 2014 I am continuously writing &amp;ldquo;a diary&amp;rdquo;. I got 5 smaller books filled already. Capturing my days, emotions, situations, thoughts, ideas, whatsoever. Mainly though it is about how I feel, what I think and what i am doing. Where I stand in life. Sometimes, maybe every couple months, I go back through some parts of them. Life never ceases to amaze me. In hindsight I see the way I took. Who I was. Who I’ve become. The areas in which I have grown. My problems, which have resolved or maybe did not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/just_another_piece/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 22:10:12 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That Special Place</title>
      <link>https://fabisblog.com/posts/that_special_place/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I close my eyes. I take a deep breath. I visit again. Here I am. At this special place. I don’t wanna write just like this. I am no academic. Maybe I am. Who even cares. I am someone close to me. To that thing. So close.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some call it the flow state. Some may even call it trance. Others, including me, like to describe it as full presence. It&amp;rsquo;s that place where no thinking takes place, just the current. The art. The moment. Creation! That’s where i am coming from. That’s where I go. That’s where I am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am no native english speaker. But that language became so dear to me. I apologize for errors. But is there some like that, I wonder? Language is like art, expressing. I came to the conclusion that self expression is so much life. Self expression feels good, is right, it may be even the core of being. So, through language, here I go. Poetically?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SELF EXPRESSION, I read in big letters right here on my desk. I wrote it down quite some time ago, in full conviction. And still, to this day, it&amp;rsquo;s SO RIGHT. I mean, the good days are filled with self expression. All of them! Think about it. Those days, when you feel uninhibited, free, self confidently saying what you think, thats great! And I wish everybody could experience more of that, BECAUSE THATS WHO WE ARE AND WHY WE ARE HERE. To self express. Beings, that express themselves freely. I love it! I love to do it as much as I love to see it in others!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The premise for self expression is self esteem. Only if we FEEL worth and appropriate to express ourselves as we are, we can live it. Self esteem might be the topic I studied most extensively in my life, for years, and hundreds of hours. What it is, where it comes from, what it does, how it works, and of course how to increase it. Self esteem is a topic I will dive very very deep into, and there might be a chunk of it in almost every post I publish. I feel like right now I could go on for hours, writing and writing… it’s that special place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fabi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <author></author>
      <guid>https://fabisblog.com/posts/that_special_place/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 21:38:19 +0100</pubDate>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>